{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Mist Cooling System Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40294/":{"taskOID":40294,"originalTaskOID":40294,"setID":594,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4742,"questionDisplayText":"Locatioin of Misting System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where/why will the misting system be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4607,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Patio area to mist plants","answerDisplayText":"Patio area to mist plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6393,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","answerDisplayText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Greenhouse in home","answerDisplayText":"Greenhouse in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6300,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Terrarium in home","answerDisplayText":"Terrarium in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2576,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"For special effects","answerDisplayText":"For special effects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6923,"questionDisplayText":"What is the approximate square footage of area to be misted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of area to be misted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4744,"questionDisplayText":"Permanent or temporary","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a permanent or temporary arrangement?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Temporary","answerDisplayText":"Temporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4742,"questionDisplayText":"Locatioin of Misting System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where/why will the misting system be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4607,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Patio area to mist plants","answerDisplayText":"Patio area to mist plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6393,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","answerDisplayText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Greenhouse in home","answerDisplayText":"Greenhouse in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6300,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Terrarium in home","answerDisplayText":"Terrarium in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2576,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"For special effects","answerDisplayText":"For special effects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4607,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Patio area to mist plants","answerDisplayText":"Patio area to mist plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6393,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","answerDisplayText":"To cool animals (kennel, barn)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Greenhouse in home","answerDisplayText":"Greenhouse in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6300,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Terrarium in home","answerDisplayText":"Terrarium in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2576,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"For special effects","answerDisplayText":"For special effects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6923,"questionDisplayText":"What is the approximate square footage of area to be misted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of area to be misted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4744,"questionDisplayText":"Permanent or temporary","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a permanent or temporary arrangement?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Temporary","answerDisplayText":"Temporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Temporary","answerDisplayText":"Temporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40294/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40294,"taskName":"Outdoor Mist Cooling System - Install","taskDescription":"Install an Outdoor Mist Cooling System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Mist Cooling System Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":171,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning Outdoor Mist air airconditioners","textMessagingName":"Mist System","rolloverLongDesc":"Used in hot parts of the country. Jets spray a barely noticeable spray into the air. The evaporation draws heat out of the air creating an area of relative coolness. Also called outdoor air conditioning.","rolloverShortDesc":"Uses mist to cool outdoor patios.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install an Outdoor Mist Cooling System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Mist Cooling System Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Outdoor Mist System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Outdoor Mist System Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Mist Cooling System - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Mist Cooling System Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Mist-Cooling-System-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Mist Cooling System Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Airconditioning,Outdoor,Mist,air,exterior,mister,misting,evaporative,cool,conditioning,ac","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":594,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}